One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Strongest Grizzly Magnum and the Assassins from Dressrosa!
Five minutes are left before the deadly
Land of Death completely fills the laboratory.
The survivors are racing for Door 66 in Building R,
which is their only escape route, but...
The ceiling just lifted for a second!
Gas is leaking in through the cracks!
Not good.
Run!
But lady, I'm scared!
Hey, this is no time to be freaking out, damn kids!
Get back on your feet and run!
Captain-chan!
I'm so glad you're safe.
So you beat the bird-lady, right?
But why are they running toward us from the front?
I thought they stayed behind to keep the enemy busy.
The G-5 troops are in front of us?
See? I told you we were going the wrong way.
Huh?!
Anyway, please put me down! This is embarrassing!
Hey you! Who the hell gave you
permission to carry Tashigi-chan?!
Zoro, you're running the wrong way!
Hurry, everyone!
This way!
Building B, 2nd floor - Laboratory
The ceiling is collapsing!
Chopperer! This place is too dangerous!
Alright. I've done everything I can.
Let's hurry to Building R!
Hang in there, Mocha! We're getting out of here!
Damn it...
How am I gonna eat breakfast tomorrow?
This is one hell of a way to take revenge.
I have to hand it to you, Law...
This is really quite upsetting.
But you will definitely regret it later.
Just remember...
You know nothing of Joker's past.
That will cost you your life.
You may have built a little reputation in this new era,
but you can easily be replaced.
The world is not as kind as you think.
Tell him, Smoker.
This world is much too complex for youngsters. You push forward on spirit alo-
You needn't worry about me. Worry about yourself instead.
This room will completely collapse soon.
So long, Pirate Vergo.
Building R, 1st floor
Only one person could do something like this...
Law!
What the hell is Vergo doing?!
Master! What is going on?!
Men are trapped under the rubble!
Master!
Dammit!
You've completely messed up my paradise!
I wonder if everyone's alright.
Building R, second floor! Can you hear me?
Secret room, respond!
We're here, Master. What just happened?
Open the air vents, right now!
Let Shinokuni flow into this room!
B-But if we do that...
I am gas. I will not die.
U-Understood.
I'll lower the elevator to get our comrades, and then-
Now!
I said to do it right now!
So quit dawdling and do it!
But there are still over a hundred soldiers down there!
Who gives a damn, dumbass!
No matter how many of you useless
guinea pigs die, nobody will miss you.
You're the scum of society!
Now quit standing around! Can't you hear me?!
I can recruit all the new subordinates I like!
Looks like they finally realize what kind of person Caesar really is.
That's Zoro and the others!
Things look bad for them.
Can they control the doors from here?
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
Oh, no reason...
Of course. I get it now!
Master is just acting, to trick the enemy!
O-Oh, I see! Yeah, that's it!
The killer gas must be part of his plan too. I mean, would he really harm his own men?
Of course not!
How could we doubt our kind Master? We must have offended him!
Master, the vents are open.
The killer gas!
It's in the building!
That's it.
You should have done what I said from the start.
Trash shouldn't try to think.
Now, become my power, Shinokuni!
Land of Death
This is the power of my research!
This will kill you.
Two countries have already taken an interest in this public demonstration of my weapon, Shinokuni!
Two utterly peaceful countries!
The moment humans start thinking about how to defend themselves,
they start longing for methods to kill their foes!
They all need me.
I will fill the world with weapons...
and become the king of Shinokuni!
Behold!
Stop...
He killed our comrades!
What is he doing?!
Master!
It's true. He only thinks of us as guinea pigs!
This is magnificent, if I do say so myself!
The sheer efficiency of this poison
is a true work of art!
W-What...
is that?!
The humans have been...
Momo, look after Brownbeard for me.
I-I will.
Hey, where are you going, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Did you suddenly get cold feet? How pathetic!
But that passage leads to Building B,
which will be flooded by Shinokuni any minute now!
There isn't a safe place left on this island!
Sorry to interrupt your moment of grief,
but I would like to use that control panel.
I want to protect my companions from the gas!
You... You saw all of that, didn't you?
You bastard!
Stop it. You all saw the same thing I saw.
Yeah, that's right. We've been betrayed!
We're done for. Even if we tried to fight back...
there's no way out of here!
But the same goes for you!
Didn't you just see
your captain run away from Caesar?!
Serves you right!
He's abandoned you to go hide somewhere!
Did I hear you right?
Did you just insult my captain to my face?
If he was just the kind of man who'd betray his crew...
that might honestly be easier for us.
But even if we want to turn tail and run...
he never, ever stops...
believing in our strength.
In the end, we always have to let him have his way!
So we have to keep on living up to his expectations,
no matter what the cost!
More than anything, Luffy hates people like Caesar.
Luffy will never forgive Caesar.
Caesar!
I'm sick of seeing your face!
Rubber...
Oh, right! Straw Hat!
What if I make you my subordina-
Grizzly Magnum!
Various Places in the New World
What's going on?
What kind of joke is this?
Public experiment, my ass.
He... defeated Caesar!
We should report this to Mama-bon.
Joker will be forced to make a move now.
Let Jack know about this.
You sure? He's not gonna like it.
This must be the work of that alliance.
Let the world know.
This isn't just a problem for the underground.
Building B, 2nd Floor
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Hang in there, Mocha.
Hey Chopper, can you hear me?
Is that Usopp's voice?
Keep going straight and then go down the stairs.
That's the fastest route to Building R.
I have to seal off Building R before the gas gets in.
Building R, 2nd Floor · The Secret Room
So you gotta hurry up.
Got it. Thanks!
Chopper-san!
Huh? Brook?!
It's terrible! Kin'emon-san was-
Kin'emon-san was hit by the deadly gas!
He's dead!
We had gone to search for Kin'emon-san's son.
We stopped to save the children
in the Inspection Room and found a certain girl.
According to that girl...
What?
Momonosuke transformed into a small dragon?
Yeah. It's a secret, but it's the truth.
Sir Corpse,
could that dragon that we recently cut down be...
Momonosuke!
I have done something unforgivable!
Kin'emon-san, you mustn't run in that direction!
The deadly gas has already come this far!
There is no path that cannot be walked, even if it's filled with fire or gas!
Momonosuke!
It is impossible, Kin'emon-san!
And that is what happened.
How could he be so reckless?
Bulding R, 1st Floor
Luffy!
Oh, Nami!
I'm so happy! You got here before us.
Brownie's collapsed on the ground.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
Oh wait. Maybe he isn't.
It is the children!
See, Momo?
The kids are fine.
My crewmates have already gone to save them.
They'll be able to handle the job.
There's no need to worry.
Hurry it up! We need get to Nami-san and everyone else!
Isn't Chopper's group here yet?
Do you think they'll make it in time, after treating the girl?
Corridor Between Buildings R and D
Is this necessary?
This is the tram they use to transport the SAD.
Everyone can use it to ride out.
We have to escape as quickly as possible.
Straw Hat.
Traf, Smoke-man!
There you are!
Hey, it's Smokey!
Eh? Smokey?
It's really him.
Thank god you're okay.
Smokey!
We have so much to talk about.
Stop fussing!
Straw Hatter, where is Caesar?
I sent him flying down that way, along with the door.
I wonder how far he flew.
You promised that you'd kidnap him!
But I don't want to catch that guy anymore.
Even if you don't want to, that was the plan.
What are you going to do if he gets away?
Who cares about that guy anyway?
Don't go changing our plans on your whims.
I shouldn't have trusted you with this.
We're going after him!
We turn back time a little.
In the sky near Punk Hazard...
When this mission is finished, so is he.
Donquixote Pirates
Servant/Assassin, Baby 5
I'll finish him off when I get back.
Weapon Fruit,
weaponized-body human
That bastard, Joker!
He killed my precious fiancé, along with an entire town!
I won't let him live!
This is the eighth time that he's killed the man
that I've promised to marry, along with eight towns!
Why does he always have to destroy my happiness?
That's how the young master shows his love.
Donquixote Pirates
Combatant, Buffalo
The young master thinks of you like a little sister.
Spin Fruit, rotating human
That's why he destroys those towns.
You should learn how to refuse proposals.
Why would I do that? He needed me!
I've fallen in love with you at first sight.
Please marry me.
You have to do something
about your habit of never turning anyone down.
It's weird that you're subscribed to fifty newspapers.
You lend people too much money,
and you're talked into buying too many things.
How much money do you owe people, now?
Shut up! I owe 98 million belly.
It's my life. Let me do what I want.
Oh, okay. Lend me two million!
He needs me!
Um... When do you need it?
I want to go to the casino when we get back.
Then I'll get you the money
as soon as we finish this mission.
I'll complete my assigned mission, but I will definitely kill that Joker.
I see it.
It's Punk Hazard!
The island is completely covered with Caesar's gas.
I wonder if I can blow up the gas.
Leave it to me! Jump up above me, Baby 5.
Behold! My power is like a typhoon.
Gust: Matasaburo!
If we wait there,
then Caesar, Monet and Vergo should come to us.
But I want to hurry home
so I can play roulette at the casino.
Did the tanker explode?
No, something ran into it.
There's a person down there.
Caesar Clown?!
Dressrosa
Joker, this is Buffalo calling from Punk Hazard.
We just arrived at Punk Hazard.
And a beaten up Master Caesar
came flying out of the island for some reason.
What's that?
Recover Caesar's body immediately and return to Dressrosa.
Huh, what about Monet and Vergo?
There must be a reason. Just do what he says.
Understood, Joker.
What a fool.
Hey you brats, heaven is my ally.
As long as I have Caesar, I can easily make more SAD.
Did you see something move on the deck of the tanker?
No, there's no way anyone could survive in that gas.
A robot?!
What kind of bird is that?
Translation & initial syncing, Yibis Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws